{
  "questionnaires": [
    {
      "question": "Java 9 main objectives are",
      "answers": [
        "To build process and maintenance of java code libraries and large applications for a JAVA SE and EE platforms.",
        "To design and implement a standard Java Platform Module System that can be easily applied to both platform and JDK.",
        "Both of the above",
        "None of the above."
      ],
      "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is correct W. R. t Java documentation?",
      "answers": [
        "Java documentation can be generated with javadoc tool.",
        "Java currently generates documentation in html 4.0 format.",
        "In java 9, we can generate documentation in html 5 format by using the-html5 option in command-line arguments.",
        "All of the above."
      ],
      "correct_answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following methods is correct about Set in Java 9?",
      "answers": [
        "For Set interfaces, from (...) Method is overloaded to have 0 to 10 parameters.",
        "For Set interfaces, from (...) Method is overloaded to have var arg as a parameter.",
        "Both above.",
        "None of the above."
      ],
      "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is an invalid member from interface to Java 8?",
      "answers": [
        "Private Method",
        "Standard method",
        "A Static Method.",
        "All of the above."
      ],
      "correct_answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is a correct statement about the takeWhile() method of the Stream class in Java 9?",
      "answers": [
        "takeWhile method takes all values until the predicate returns false.",
        "In the case of the ordered stream, there is a stream that consists of the longest prefix of elements originating from that stream corresponding to the given predicate.",
        "Both of the above",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "explain the following allocation algorithms: Best fit",
      "answers": [
        "In the best fit approach, it is to assign the first free partition or hole large enough that can accommodate the process. It ends after finding the first suitable free partition.",
        "In best-fit approach, it is possible to find largest available free portion so that the remaining part is large enough to be useful. It is the back of the best fit.",
        "The best-fit-deals with the allocation of the smallest free partition, which meets the requirement of the requesting process. "
      ],
      "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is a correct statement about try-with-resources statement in Java 9?",
      "answers": [
        "Before Java 9, resources must be declared before try or in try.",
        "In Java 9, resources do not have to be declared before try or inside try statement.",
        "Both above.",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the purpose of the Optional class?",
      "answers": [
        "To avoid null checks ",
        "In order to avoid NullPointerException-problems ",
        "Both of the above",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "correct_answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following describes the getresolution variants () method of the multi-resolution image-interface, correct?",
      "answers": [
        "Retrieves a specific image that is the best way to display this logical image at the specified size.",
        "Retrieves a human-readable list of all resolution variants.",
        "Both of the above",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "correct_answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following describes the defaultExecutor() method of CompletableFuture Interface correctly?",
      "answers": [
        "This method completes this CompletableFuture with the specified value if not before the specified timeout.",
        "This completes this exceptionally completable future with a timeout exception, if it is not completed before the specified timeout.",
        "Returns a new incomplete CompletableFuture of the type to be returned by a CompletionStage method.",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "correct_answer": 2
    }
  ]
}